So now let's talk about Amazon QApps.
QApps are part of Q Business,
and the idea is that you can create
Genai-powered apps without
coding by only using natural language.
So we have a web UI called Amazon QApps Creator,
and in there, you can specify
a prompt to describe the type of app you want to have.
Again, this app is going to be based on your company data.
So you're going to say, "Hey, I want to do this kind of app,
and automatically Amazon QApp is going to generate
for you a web application where we can, for example,
upload a document, and then upload prompts and so on,
and our users can use this app.
So it really makes it super easy for anyone in your company
to create an app based on your company's internal data,
as well as leveraging plugins.
So anyone can create a very quick app without using developers,
and that's the idea behind Amazon QApps.
But I think it's best if you see it in action,
So I will see you in the next lecture for a practice on Amazon QMs.